Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Previously on
Strange New Worlds...
I'm gonna give
you a sedative now.
And when you wake up.
you will be Gorn-free.
I'm still here.
You are going to make it.
I'm Erica Ortegas.
I fly the ship.
Fraternization can
lead to complications.
Like I've been trying
to tell you. I just need
-some personal time.
-Away from me.
About that fellowship. the
archaeological medicine?
I'm going to have to
replace you. aren't I?
The thought
of losing you.
it affected me deeply.
I am still going
away for three months
to study with Roger Korby.
When I get back. let's
just see where we are then.
Science
officer's personal log.
star date 2251.7.
After a three-month
billet at Starbase One.
the battle scars
of our encounter
with the Gorn are
all but erased.
which has left me with a
great deal of time to think.
The Federation Day Centennial...
the 100th anniversary
of the founding
of the United
Federation of Planets...
is just three days away.
Captain Pike believes that
hosting a ceremonial gala
for Federation Day will
improve morale among the crew.
All of the crew.
Nurse Chapel is returning
from her time away.
We have not spoken since
she left for her fellowship.
As such. I have a more
personal reason to prepare
for the upcoming celebrations.
Loosen up your shoulders.
My shoulder placement has
been measured precisely.
You're not supposed
to measure them.
You're supposed
to let them flow.
Like this.
I am confused.
Am I not already
performing the movements
to the parameters you specified?
Yes. You're just stiff.
Even for you.
Five. six. seven. and...
Please do not take
this the wrong way.
but your aptitude
for this activity
is surprising. and
if I may say so.
this openness to new life
experiences suits you.
There was a time when
I wanted nothing more
than to be a prima ballerina.
I assume the Gorn changed that?
That's just it. I've
spent my whole life
waiting for them to come back.
My own personal
nightmare under the bed.
And here's the
thing... they came back
and I beat them. Anyway...
somehow
the Gorn are less ravenous
than prima ballerinas.
Perhaps that is why Vulcans.
as a rule. do not dance.
It seems some of you will defy
that rule for the right person.
When humans reunite after a long
absence. is it not tradition
to make a grand
romantic gesture?
Spock. I-I don't want to pry.
but I thought you and
Christine had decided
-to give each other some space.
-Indeed.
We have not spoken since
she left for her fellowship.
But we all know what absence
does to the heart. mm-hmm.
The absence of a heart
would be quite fatal.
No. Spock. it's
an idiom. it's...
Mm-hmm.
Enterprise
to Mr. Spock.
You asked for a
heads-up. so. heads up.
Transport clearance
request from Nurse Chapel.
Please excuse me. She is here.
Looking good. Mr. Spock.
Lieutenant?
Just doing my job.
Chapel added someone
to the visitors list.
Curious.
That's funny.
You know. for a wee
moment there. I thought
I saw a bit of strangeness.
What sort
of strangeness?
Oh. just a sensor
ghost outside the hull.
But it's gone now.
Nothing to see here. sir. hmm.
All relevant scans appear to
be within normal parameters.
Two to beam aboard.
Lieutenant Scott.
Spock.
Christine.
Uh. this is Dr. Korby.
-Your fellowship director?
-Mm-hmm.
Greetings. Dr. Korby.
How are you? Call me Roger.
I've. uh. heard a
lot about you. Spock.
Dr. Korby. I have
read a considerable number
of your papers on
archaeological medicine.
-Oh. sure. there aren't that many.
-There are
234. Is that not accurate?
It's actually exactly
how many there are.
Wow.
Is that a first
edition of Saltavantur?
May I?
This is incredible.
The engravings alone
must date back to...
It is a gift for Christine.
Wow.
Well. welcome aboard. Dr. Korby.
Will you be needing quarters?
Uh. no. no. I'm. um...
I'm taken care of.
He is here
to attend the centennial
celebration with me.
With you?
Dr. Korby is my date.
Space.
The final frontier.
These are the voyages of
the starship Enterprise.
Its five-year mission:
to explore strange new worlds...
...to seek out new life
and new civilizations...
...to boldly go where
no one has gone before.
Okay.
Come on. baby boy.
You can't handle the haymaker.
Who even says that?
Don't get cocky. I'll land one.
-Aah!
-Hey!
I told you to turn
that camera off.
-I'm just doing my job.
-Yeah. your job
is a documentary on
the centennial gala.
not this workout.
I am a serious filmmaker.
Erica. ah. there you are.
You are not going
to believe this.
-Christine brought home a date.
-Chapel?
I'm just as
shocked as you are.
Hey.
Hi. I'm. uh...
Haymaker!
Uh...
Okay. who's this?
That's
my little brother.
Never could take a punch.
Hi.
I'm Nyota.
All right. almost done.
Take your time. Ensign.
With all the centennial
preparations I have to do.
this is the closest thing
to a vacation I'm gonna get.
Well. this is the last one.
but I can take a bunch more.
I mean. how much blood
does a person really need?
They didn't cover that
in nursing school?
Oof. I fell asleep.
Like. a lot.
I like you. Ensign.
Well. now that Nurse
Chapel is back.
my temporary assignment is done.
I wouldn't be so sure.
Don't look at me.
Take it up with your
direct supervisor.
Guilty as charged.
I put in a request
with Starfleet Medical
to make your transfer permanent.
Wait. wait. please tell me
this isn't a cruel joke.
We are big on cruel
jokes around here.
Just wait until your first
formal Captain's Table.
But in this case. no.
Apparently. he isn't
ready to give you up.
Frankly. none of us are. Ensign.
Thank you.
Captain Batel is
lucky to have you.
How's Marie doing?
Her scans show that the
Gorn embryos have been
fully reabsorbed.
It was your blood
that kept her body
strong enough to survive
the metabolization process.
All we're doing now is managing
some minor aftereffects.
I've gotten used to
having her on board.
I'll be sorry to see her go.
I imagine you won't
be the only one.
I have literally
no idea what some of
these medals are for.
And I can't wear all
of them. or can I?
-Pick one.
-No.
Because then I would
insult whoever gave me
the ones I'm not wearing
and...
Must be hard being such
an amazing captain.
You. uh...
shopping for a new starship?
Admiral April said
I've got my pick.
There are about a dozen
commissions available.
Okay.
So. what are you looking for?
Deep space exploration.
But then I never see you.
Or short-range
diplomatic courier.
But then I still never see you.
It still doesn't
feel totally real.
Hmm?
I should be dead. I'm...
I'm on borrowed time.
Well. you're preaching
to the choir on that one.
Now I'm just picturing
you in a boys' choir.
Actually. I was an altar
boy.
You're a captain.
You'll find your ship.
I just wish it didn't
have to be so soon.
What are you asking me. Captain?
Frankly. I don't know. I...
All I know is that
I'm not ready to let you go.
Well. this is awkward.
Right. sorry.
-It was too far. That...
-Relax.
I was just wondering
what you're gonna do
when I move you
into my quarters.
-Oh.
-Where will all your hair products go?
Mmm.
Hey.
I-I brought this.
I thought you
might want it back.
It was a gift.
Why would I not wish
for you to have it?
I'm sorry about earlier.
I didn't want you to
meet Roger like that.
The look of surprise
on your face
was almost worth the misstep.
This isn't easy.
May I ask you a direct question?
Never known you to
be any different.
You expressed the desire
to remain unattached.
free of commitment.
And then I bring
my new boyfriend
home for the holidays.
Yes.
Uh...
When I figure that
out for myself.
I swear you will
be the first person
that I explain it to.
The truth is. I don't know.
It just is.
Spock.
Are we gonna be okay?
Um...
We're having cocktails in
the Port Galley tonight.
I hope you'll come.
Fine. one drink. then I have
to go back and finish training.
Aren't you the one who taught me
tequila is its own food group?
You realize she's our
communications officer. right?
She speaks. like. 900 languages.
Is "obnoxious big
sister" one of 'em?
Let it go. Beto. You
can hang with me.
That seems like a plan to me.
Wait one damn minute.
This. you two...
...talking to each
other like you're...
and looking at each
No. It's chaos. madness.
You don't trust me
with your best friend?
with your baby brother?
Okay. Okay. I'll
stay for a while.
But there will be
no more flirting.
Literally none.
So. Dr. Korby.
Uh. Sam. I got to
say. I'm a big fan
of your work on advanced
ancient cultures.
-I read that your latest dig was on Vadia Nine.
-Uh-huh.
Uh. have you
climbed Mount Caleb?
Uh. we did. actually. Yeah.
It was. it was
pretty romantic. actually.
Uh. Mr. Spock.
Glad you could join us.
I finished my work early.
Dr. Korby was just about to
tell us a romantic story.
-Oh. no. don't worry about it.
-No.
-Some other time.
-You guys don't want to hear...
-Bore the life out of you.
-Yeah.
I would
like to hear it.
I have. of late. become
a student of romance.
Sudden thirst. Beto. give
me a hand with some drinks.
Okay. Um... Well.
uh. when I was a little girl.
whenever I would go
away on a trip...
to camp. to school...
my mother would
always say to me.
"Chrissy. I hope
you find the sun..."
"I hope you find the sun
and the moon and the stars."
Yeah.
And they turned out
to be the last words
she ever said to me.
And. um.
Mount Caleb actually happens
to break the solar plane.
So. um. the sun and the moon
are visible at the same time.
And it was my mother's birthday.
And I didn't tell anybody
'cause I never do.
Uh. but he just noticed
that I was down and...
remembered the story and
put two and two together.
And when we got to the top...
When we got to the top.
I showed her the stunning sky
and gave her this.
Tilaryan Star Gems.
-They're incredibly rare.
-Yeah.
And he said.
"You looked sad.
I wanted to give you the sun
and the moon and the stars."
-Libations.
-Shots. everybody!
-Fun.
-Thank God.
Ooh. that's a cool bracelet.
Where'd you get it?
Good evening.
Ready for a change?
I was not aware we had
a Vulcan bartender.
Temporary posting.
Just passing through.
So. something
different but better?
Something you definitely want?
Yes. that would be fine.
Fantastic.
I have just the thing.
Swirl it around.
Brings out the aroma.
Don't drink it too fast.
It'll go right to your head.
Hmm.
Good morning.
Good morning back.
Tonight. no sleepover.
It is bad luck to see your bride
on the day of your wedding.
Science
Officer's personal log.
Stardate 2251.7.
After a three-month billet.
the battle scars of our
encounter with the Gorn
are all but erased.
And while docked
at Starbase One.
our crew prepares to celebrate
a rare and joyous occasion.
the wedding nuptials between
myself and Nurse Chapel.
Your first dance
is going to be great.
You're improving.
Untrue.
I've never understood
the need for deception
to smooth a potential
negative reaction.
You're just going
to excel at marriage.
Have you ever been married?
Me? God no.
I'm not really the
commitment type.
My childhood didn't really set
me up for a stable attachment.
Now. shooting backwards
while running.
that I can do.
Of late. I must say you
have seemed lighter.
Spock. if you don't
have it by now.
then it's too late.
Thank you. La'An.
You have been a
good friend to me.
I must prepare
for the rehearsal.
Places. everyone!
We have much to do.
A wedding doesn't just plan
itself overnight. you know.
And the rehearsal is
just like the real thing.
only with comfortable shoes.
This wedding planner
of yours is something.
Never thought of Andorians
as being so detail-oriented.
Hmm.
You two. you're
like two peas in a space pod.
So delightful.
-Let's start with the cake.
-Wait. uh. where's Roger?
I feel like we should
probably wait for my best man.
I'm here.
I am here.
And I have the cakes.
-Excellent.
-Oh. yeah. Very nice.
Christine. I
couldn't just chat...
Uh. later. Mr. Korby.
Doctor.
-Dr. Korby.
-Fine.
Actually. I have a
special best man task
just for you.
Could you wait for
me way over there?
Quick as you can.
Good one. Now. Mr. Spock.
I know you wanted to embrace
a human-type wedding.
but what about fusion style?
I call this "Hu-can."
Or "Vul-man."
Just try it.
You hate it?
I was not expecting cake with
quite so much heat and brine.
Let's try that again. shall we?
Oh. I'll go.
Spock's joking.
this is delicious.
Is it chocolate and. um...
Vulcan pahklor?
Indeed. pahklor.
Nothing says love like pahklor.
I must've
been mistaken before.
This is quite good.
Not just good but perfect.
like your wedding
is going to be.
Let's talk about choreography.
Spock. assuming we're not going
to have a Kal-if-ee situation.
I have you over on the altar
and your best man Captain
Pike in the front row
just here.
Joseph and Una.
I see you waltzing
Christine down the aisle
and then spin her
into Spock's arms.
I didn't practice that.
I have a surprise for
you. my blushing bride.
Arrived all the way
from Vermont. Earth
this morning.
My mother's flowers?
She had these preserved
after her wedding.
Oh. no.
Those
flowers look dead.
These were supposed to be
stored at exactly 2.7 degrees.
-I mean. the...
-I'm so sorry. Christine.
Is there any way
to salvage them?
I-I have a rehydrator
in my quarters.
I'll tell you what.
Maybe they just need to breathe.
I mean...
Oh. my God.
What?
It worked. I can't believe it.
This is why we have rehearsal.
And with that avertation
of the latest crisis.
let's continue.
With both at the altar.
we have the rings
exchanged. and voilà.
Everyone's as happy
as a Ternaran bat.
Uh. Christine. can we just
chat for two seconds. please?
Unfortunately. rehearsal
has just finished.
which means. Nurse Chapel. I'm
gonna have to scoop you away
for your final fitting.
So quickly. here we go.
Please tell me you're not gonna
wear that jacket on the day.
Korbs.
Hey. how are you?
How're you doing?
Dr. Korby. what are you doing?
I'm. um...
...trying to delete your vows.
I knew it. The
cake. the flowers.
you are trying to
sabotage our wedding.
Yeah. y-you can't
marry Christine.
Are you in love with her?
Yes. But that's not the reason.
Well. not entirely.
Look. this wedding is not
supposed to happen. okay?
Uh. I can't fully explain it.
but our reality has shifted.
-I think you should leave. Doctor.
-Just listen.
Yesterday. Christine and I
arrived on the Enterprise
to attend the
Federation's Centennial.
We specifically chose the
centennial as our wedding day.
No. no. no. no. It is
the reason we are here.
As of yesterday.
there was no wedding.
There was no "you
and Nurse Chapel."
She and I were together.
You arrived together because
you are best friends.
No. not as best friends.
romantically we are together.
But I seem to be the only
one here that remembers that.
I proposed to Christine
three months ago.
before she embarked on
her fellowship with you.
I procured my grandmother's
engagement ring...
None of that happened.
Why am I the only one
that remembers this?
You parted ways
before the fellowship.
And yeah. when I met her. at
first. she was pretty gloomy.
I get it. endings
are... are difficult.
I think you should
visit sickbay. Doc...
Wait.
At first. she was a fellow. yes.
But she quickly became more.
An equal.
After a while. she was
running the excavation site
on Vadia Nine with me.
And one night. we stayed late.
And I read her a poem by Neruda.
"I crave your mouth.
your voice. your hair."
And she. um...
She kissed me...
Oh. no.
Please. Dr. Korby.
I owe you an apology.
Yes. for that. But
also. you were right.
Reality has been changed.
None of this is
how it should be.
-So you remember?
-I do.
But I am not entirely sure why.
Have you tried
telling Christine?
Yes. but she shut me down.
I've considered several
possible explanations
for this mass delusion.
First. that this is an
alternate dimension.
I've already checked myself for
phase variance and found none.
Exposure to an
environmental hallucinogen.
Christine and I arrived
at the same time. so...
You would both be unaffected.
Alien virus?
The bio-filters have
been recently upgraded.
Perhaps an improbability field?
We once entered one
that made us... sing.
Perhaps.
Now that I am aware
of the situation.
I will obviously not
proceed with the nuptials.
You may not have a choice.
Every time I've tried
to stop this wedding.
something has interfered.
You are suggesting the presence
of an advanced
intelligent life-form
with reality-altering
capabilities.
Yes.
But why leave you unaffected?
Well...
...my rigorous
intellect may have
shielded my mind
from the illusion.
Doctor.
If one of our intellects
could bestow immunity.
I am confident it
would not be yours.
Come. We can use the science
lab to scan the ship.
Any anomalous energy
should be detectable.
Great. Another
Andorian annoyance.
Ah. there you are!
Greetings and many felicitations
on this happiest
of wedding eves.
-Oh. Mr. Korby.
-Doctor.
You really are
everywhere. aren't you?
Bit like a rash.
Speaking of which. the
rest of the bridal party
are enjoying facials.
Perhaps you should join them.
You do look a little
dull. Are you sleeping?
The bags beneath
your eyes say no.
My darling groom. what
do you think of this?
The color really
brings out your eyes.
Could this wait? I have
urgent duties to attend to.
Don't be silly.
Right now. your most important
mission is matrimony.
That one will be fine.
Come. We must go.
It's Doctor.
"It's Doctor."
Nice lab.
Initiating ship-wide scan now.
It will take a few minutes.
I was thinking about how it was
that you became disillusioned.
At the moment I punched you.
it was as if a fog
in my mind lifted.
and I knew.
Perhaps it was the sudden burst
of adrenaline and
cortisol that did it.
It is also possible
that whatever power
is creating this false
reality cannot be maintained
when so directly
confronted with the truth.
Regardless. we must find a way
to communicate the
situation to the captain.
Good luck with that.
There you are.
You were supposed to
meet me in your quarters.
Whatever this is. I cannot.
Sam! What do we have here?
These are the wine selections
for the head table tomorrow.
Listen to me very
carefully. Lieutenant Kirk.
Enterprise came to Starbase One
to celebrate the
Federation Centennial.
Not a wedding.
Nurse Chapel and I are
no longer a couple.
We are not getting married.
You are suffering from
an unknown phenomenon.
It is possible we
are all under attack.
I get it.
I get it. Spock.
you have cold feet.
-It's totally normal. look...
-Punch me.
What?
I'm not gonna punch you.
You are sloppy.
Less intelligent
than your brother.
No one likes your mustache.
And you have terrible
taste in wine.
If I gave you a black eye
the day before your wedding.
Christine would kill me.
Scan complete.
There are no anomalous
energy readings present.
Perhaps the chardonnay.
Sir. we have an
urgent situation.
I am aware. Lieutenant.
And there. Fixed that.
Mr. Spock. welcome to
your bachelor party.
-Hey.
-Spock-o!
Spock!
I prepared all
of your favorites.
Jumbo mollusk. Pok-tar.
and look what I found.
Lutrog.
And something imbibable for
the rest of us: Saurian brandy.
Hmm?
Oh. honestly. I'm not
really much of a drinker.
I hardly touch the stuff.
I believe tradition dictates
the groom-to-be give us a toast
before he walks the plank.
-Yes. speech.
-Speech.
Come on. Mr. Spock.
Our reality has been changed.
Nurse Chapel and I
are not together.
She is in love with Dr. Korby.
and only he and I remember this.
To Spock. the luckiest
man in the world.
Yes. to Spock.
-Mr. Spock.
-Cheers.
Captain. Enterprise is
experiencing a mass delusion.
I told you. Cold feet.
My feet are perfectly
warm. thank you.
This is serious.
Relax. Mr. Spock.
Which I know is
difficult for you.
That's why the Lutrog.
Careful with that.
It seems clear by now
that being confronted
with the truth
is not enough to
break the spell.
Which leaves us with
emotional response.
But we have seen a
range of emotions
and yet none dispel
the delusion.
Anger. rage. it's one of the
most powerful emotions there is.
Perhaps another equally
powerful emotion.
Like what?
Love.
Mr. Spock. I almost
forgot. the wedding planner
asked you to weigh in on
the seating arrangement.
Take a look at row
eight. if you don't mind.
Uh. Captain?
How many guests are
invited to the wedding?
All the crew and. uh.
107 registered guests.
Thanks.
Computer. how many individuals
are currently aboard
the Enterprise
besides crew and
registered guests?
One.
We have a wedding crasher.
Hiding in plain sight.
Computer. locate
that individual.
The individual
fitting that description
is in the Port Galley.
Spock. where you going?
We're gonna do karaoke.
Oh.
Mr. Korby. Mr. Spock.
Shouldn't you be at
your bachelor party?
I'm working on a specialty
drink for the reception.
How do we feel
about pomegranate?
I do not need a bacchanal.
Then you should get
your beauty rest.
I do not need to sleep.
Count tribbles. then.
You. You are the entity.
Oh. Mr. Spock.
Your Vulcan sense of
humor gets me every time.
I'm your wedding
planner. remember?
You twirled into my
office. drunk on love.
wishing for a wedding day full
of magic and unspeakable joy.
A wish.
That night. here
in the Port Galley.
you were the
bartender then. too.
I wished things could be
different with Christine.
And you made it so.
You're welcome.
It does not matter.
We are not going through
with the wedding.
You have to fix this.
You can't just control
people's minds.
I can do anything I want.
I am a wedding planner.
And I do not like it when
people ruin my plans.
Wakey wakey. Mr. Spock.
It's your big day.
You cannot force me to
continue this charade.
Can't I. though? Do you know
what would happen to
everyone if you made me mad?
I don't think I can
even imagine it.
Well. look at that.
My own little Vulcan terrarium.
My friends will be so jealous.
I do hope you'll
play along now. yes?
I can
hear the wedding bells.
Ah! Look at you. you look great.
All weddings should
be on the beach
and everyone should
be in shorts.
Okay.
I have been searching for you.
He's made me the maid of honor.
And he says if I
don't play along.
he's gonna wish us
all to a cornfield.
I do not understand the
significance of this wish.
It's from a... Doesn't matter.
He's talking about wiping
us from all of existence.
Yes. he made this
threat to me as well.
You're gonna have to
go through with this.
Just... Maybe that's
the only way to end it.
play his game.
It's time. Spock.
Let's get you married.
Please be seated.
What a delight
to be gathered here today to
celebrate something so special.
a force more powerful
than the fastest starship.
Humans call it love.
and I'm told love can conquer
-all things.
-Christine...
Shh. Not yet.
Do you both have your vows?
No.
No!
I object.
-We're not there yet.
-Roger. what are you doing?
Christine. you
have to stop this.
You stop.
You can't just make
people feel things
that they don't really feel!
That's it.
Aw...
Please. continue. Mr. Spock.
The human poet Neruda wrote.
"I crave your mouth. your voice.
"your hair.
"Silent and starving.
"I prowl through the streets.
"Bread does not nourish me.
"dawn disrupts me.
"all day
I hunt for the liquid
measure of your steps."
This is what it is like
to love you. Christine.
And the person
worthy of your love.
they must be courageous.
They cannot be drowning.
They cannot be unsure
or at the mercy of their
own emotional storms.
They must be a safe harbor.
They must have the ability
to hold space for you.
To see you.
Just you.
They must be able to
hear your unuttered call.
give you everything.
They must offer you the moon
and the sun and the stars
all at once.
I did not know when it was
your mother's birthday.
I didn't tell you.
It's no one's fault.
This is wrong. Spock.
We're not supposed to
be getting married.
No.
We are not.
Yes. you are.
Roger...
Roger.
Well. no. he's a dog.
so... No!
No. no. no. no. no!
That is it.
Everybody dies.
-And I'm starting with the dog.
-You keep away from him.
Prepare for a
cavalcade of death.
No one gets a wedding
cake slice tonight.
You're going to
die. You'll be dead.
And you with the crown.
what were you thinking?
Tried to outshine the bride?
And you blue faces. you
could see I was in blue.
How dare you.
Death to you. And
you at the back
with no mouth.
Yes. you.
Actually. that's... I like
that. You can. you can live.
What is this?
Not now. Dad.
Oh. you've
made enough of a mess.
Please. let's not make a scene.
Oh. my...
-Christine.
-Oh. Oh...
But they're not playing along.
They're not listening to me.
And you
are not listening to me.
Shall I show you once more
what the consequence is
-for disobedience?
-No.
I'll be good. I promise.
Wait. you're a child?
A very young one. Only
8.000 of your Earth years.
8.020. Dad.
-It's time to go.
-I don't want to go.
Wait. before you leave...
...might I ask why?
Well...
Look at him.
I spotted him digging in the
dirt on the old homeworld.
He's just so handsome
and smart and perfect.
It's just annoying.
Yes. that does
make perfect sense.
-Oy.
-Now...
-free the rest of them.
-Okay.
Tallyho.
You've all been lots of fun.
Uh...
Okay. everybody. all
right. all right.
all right. all right.
okay. all right.
That was. uh. that-that-that...
that was strange.
A shared delusion
about a wedding
is a new one. isn't
it?
Okay... Uh. Federation Day.
2161. the. uh. founding species
came together to create.
uh. the Federation.
Um. largely in response
to our interactions with
other foreign species.
Some of them very awkward.
Uh. so it's only fitting
that-that our-our
centennial be marked
by a-a-a similar awkward.
uh. interaction.
And the bar is open.
Those
look incredible.
I'll make you
one. but it's Alanni Rye.
It will burn a hole
through your esophagus
and whatever is
below your esophagus.
And maybe the floor.
Two pints of Guinness. please.
Probably a safer bet.
Are you the doctor
from the Enterprise?
Joseph M'Benga.
Mm.
You know. I kind of
miss the flower crown.
-Oh. yeah?
-Mm.
I kind of miss the
big green veil thing
you had going on.
Well. I can tell you it
is not every girl's dream
to have a cosmic trickster
play dress-up dolls
with her emotions
and make her marry
the wrong man.
-The last 48 hours have been...
-Roger.
I know.
Me. too.
Now. let's go dance and
never talk about this
ever.
Deal.
You thinking what I'm thinking?
Mm-hmm. If we
play our cards right.
Oh. we were just
saying that an artist
with such prodigious skills
shouldn't be confined
to a starbase.
If you're offering me
a job on a starship.
my answer is yes.
Thank you.
-Pleasure meeting you.
-Thank you.
I just had a very
interesting conversation
with the Chancellor of
Starfleet's Public Relations.
-Yeah?
-They may commission
a feature-length
documentary of Starfleet.
Well. the Chancellor likes me.
so I'll put in a good word.
You know. anything
to annoy Erica.
-Shall we annoy Erica?
-To annoying Erica.
-Mm-hmm.
That was a beautiful speech.
Yes. I suppose so.
Love comes in all
forms. Mr. Spock.
and you gave her yours.
And I have no regrets.
Still. it is a waste.
What is?
Well. you spent all this
time learning to dance.
and now you're just
sitting on it.
After all. your
shoulder placement
has been measured
precisely. has it not?
If I'm not mistaken.
I am not supposed
to measure them.
I am supposed to let them flow.
Lieutenant...
are you asking me to dance?
♪ Jitterbug ♪
It's all you. It's all you.
♪ You put the boom
boom into my heart ♪
♪ You send my soul sky high
when your loving starts ♪
-♪ Jitterbug into my brain ♪
-♪ Yeah. yeah ♪
♪ Goes a bang-bang-bang
till my feet do the same ♪
♪ But something's bugging
me. something ain't right ♪
♪ My best friend told me
what you did last night ♪
♪ Left me sleeping in my bed ♪
♪ I was dreaming ♪
♪ But I should've been
with you instead ♪
♪ Wake me up before you go-go ♪
♪ Don't leave me hanging
on like a yo-yo ♪
♪ Wake me up before you go-go ♪
♪ I don't want to miss it
when you hit that high ♪
♪ Wake me up before you go-go ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm not
planning on going solo ♪
♪ Wake me up before you go-go ♪
♪ Take me dancing tonight ♪
♪ I want to hit that high. ♪
Captioning sponsored by CBS
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm